const STORE = [
	{
		question: 'What is the first thing you should do when you change an apparatus?',
		answers: ['Untying the wraps, starting with the locking wraps.', 'Give the line you’re working with a tug to make sure you’re on the correct line.', 'Tell everyone what you’re doing.', 'Do the rig dance.'], 
		correctAnswer: 'Give the line you’re working with a tug to make sure you’re on the correct line.'

	},
	{
		question: 'For our pinrail system, how many regular wraps do you tie?',
		answers: ['3', '2', '1', '4'],
		correctAnswer: '2'
	},

	{
		question: 'For our pinrail system, how many locking wraps do you tie?',
		answers: ['3', '2', '1', 'all'],
		correctAnswer: '2'
	},

	{
		question: 'Why is it important that everyone tie off the pinrails with the same number and type of wraps?',
		answers: ['It looks nicer.', 'If an aerial rescue needs to happen, the person doing the rescue will automatically know the number of wraps.', 'It doesn’t matter.', 'None of the above.'],
		correctAnswer: 'If an aerial rescue needs to happen, the person doing the rescue will automatically know the number of wraps.'
	},

	{
		question: 'What are common aerial rescue situations?',
		answers: ['Aerialist getting tangled in the silks or stuck in the trapeze ropes.', 'Clothing getting caught.', 'Fear of heights.', 'All of the above.'],
		correctAnswer: 'All of the above.'
	},

	{
		question: 'Why do we tie two regular wraps on the pinrail (before the locking ones)?',
		answers: ['It takes less time than doing 4 locking wraps.', 'It looks nicer.', 'It helps with aerial rescue.', 'None of the above.'],
		correctAnswer: 'It helps with aerial rescue.'
	},

		{
		question: 'What are the triangles used for in rigging?',
		answers: ['Single point trapeze.', 'Double point lyra.', 'Both of the above.', 'None of the above.'],
		correctAnswer: 'Both of the above.'
	},

	{
		question: 'Which way should you rig a carabiner?',
		answers: ['So that it “screws down” (top down).', 'So that it “screws up” (top up).', 'Either.', 'None of the above.'],
		correctAnswer: 'So that it “screws down” (top down).'
	},

	{
		question: 'What should you consider when storing silks, ropes, and hammocks?',
		answers: ['Daisy chain when not in use.', 'Make sure they are not touching the floor.', 'Hang them by the rescue 8.', 'All of the above.'],
		correctAnswer: 'All of the above.'
	},

	{
		question: 'What should you do if you’re not 100% sure how to rig an apparatus?',
		answers: ['Rig with your best guess solution, it’s probably fine.', 'Check-in with another Sky Candy rig trained employee.', 'Refer to the Staff Rigging Training powerpoint.', 'Both/either B &C.'],
		correctAnswer: 'Both/either B &C.'
	},



]